# ANDREW XING **EXPERIENCE DESIGNER**

#### Thingsbyxing.com

Andrew.xing1@gmail.com

#### 0432 854 289

#### **DESIGN EXPERIENCE**

# UX/UI INTERNSHIP Ai Ps :

ENZO4D | 2021-PRESENT

Redesigned the layout and flow of the existing web app and site through research and user-testing.

Collaborated with others in the team in the iterating. prototyping and wireframing of the final user interface.

# UX/UI VOLUNTEER :

**GET2KNOW** | 2021-PRESENT

Volunteered design skills to rebrand and develop website for healthcare case manager

Created several UX artifacts to understand customer journey, whilst working in an agile UX environment

#### **DESIGN PROJECTS**

## WEB APP DEVELOPMENT AI IM F



Awarded the 2020 Industry Awards Shortlist Award.

Designed and produced a simulation web application with interactive and 3D animated elements.

Final product is informative and research-based. Methods used included user research, market analysis and data research.

### USER INTERFACE DESIGN AI M ?







#### **PETBOARD**

Created a comprehensive user interface and prototype of the usability of the app. Realistic mock-ups of the app were also produced.

Collaborated and worked within a team environment. managing deadlines and encouraging teammates

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF DESIGN COMPUTING**

University of Sydney 2018-2020

Studied user experience research and design, as well as other interface, product and service design

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

#### **ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT**

**Miramar Accountants** 2021

#### **SCRIPTURE TEACHER**

**SCRIPTURE UNION 2018-2019** 

#### **TUTOR**

**CORNERSTONE EDUCATION 2018-2019** 

#### **SKILLS** TOOLS Figma UX/UI Design

| Λ | <b>Adobe Suite</b> | Visual Design |
|---|--------------------|---------------|

| X | HTML/CSS     | Web Design/Coding |
|---|--------------|-------------------|
|   | TITIVIL/ CSS | web besign/coding |

| 1 | Microsoft<br>Office | Video Editing |
|---|---------------------|---------------|

| Asana | Project Management |
|-------|--------------------|
|-------|--------------------|



### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

2020 Biodesign Challenge Finalist

2020 Industry Awards Shortlist

\$7,000 New Colombo Plan Scholarship Recipient